Guide to the Amber Arthun Warburton Papers, 1917-1976 and undated RL.01341
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Institute of Social and Religious Research Series, 1929-1930
  - United States Children's Bureau Series, 1929-1944
    - Alliance for Guidance of Rural Youth Series, 1922-1966
      - Green Sea
        - Material Related to Guidance in a Rural Community
          - Manuscript Edited by Ruth Strang (Box 57, Folder 1)
          - Manuscript Edited by Howard Dawson (Box 57, Folder 2)
          - Edited Manuscript (Box 57, Folder 3)
          - Edited Manuscript (Box 57, Folder 4)
          - Edited Manuscript (Box 57, Folder 5)
          - Edited Manuscript (Box 57, Folder 6)
          - Galley Sheets (Box 57, Folder 7)
          - Galley Sheets (Box 57, Folder 8)
          - Photographs (Box 57, Folder 9)
          - Photographs (Box 58, Folder 1)
          - Photographs (Box 58, Folder 2)
          - Copies of Photographs (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Darlington County (S.C.) Project. Correspondence,1951 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Darlington County Project. Accompanying Material,1951 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Scope of Alliance for Guidance of Rural Youth Program,1949 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Farm Labor News, 1946-1950 (Oversize-folder 1)
      - Department of Agricultural Releases, 1947 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - National Citizens Council for Migrant Labor
        In 1947 a group of individuals and organizations formed a council to study problems of migrant labor, the National Citizens Council for Migrant Labor. The council not only studied the problems of migrant labor, but also lobbied Congress, monitored federal and state agencies, and publicized key issues on behalf of migrant laborers. Warburton was a founding member of the council, and served on its board of directors from 1947 to 1960. In 1953 she supervised a field study of migrant laborers in the Belle Glade section of Palm Beach County, Florida. Her findings were incorporated into the book, The Education of Migrant Children, by Shirley E. Greene. A copy of the book is in Box 27.
        In 1950 the council expanded its scope to include problems of everyone involved in agriculture in the United States. Consequently, the council changed its name to the National Citizens Council on Agricultural Life and Labor. For ease of organization, all material has been grouped under the heading, National Citizens Council for Migrant Labor.
        - Correspondence and Accompanying Material
          - 1944-1945 (Box 81)
          - 1947 (Box 58, Folder 8)
          - 1948 (Box 59, Folder 1)
          - 1949 (Box 59, Folder 2)
          - 1950 (Box 59, Folder 3)
          - 1951 (Box 59, Folder 4)
          - 1952 (Box 59, Folder 5)
          - 1953 (Box 59, Folder 6)
          - 1954 (Box 59, Folder 7)
          - 1955-1960and undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
        - Bulletins and Newsletters, 1950-1952 (Box 60, Folder 1)
        - Bulletins and Newsletters, 1953-1958 (Box 60, Folder 2)
        - Printed Material Received by the NCCML, 1950-1959 (Box 80, Box 60, Folder 3)
        - Research Fund, Incorporated. Correspondence and Accompanying Material, 1955-1960 (Box 60, Folder 4)
        - Material Related to The Education of Migrant Children
          - Correspondence, 1952-1957 (Box 60, Folder 5)
          - Minutes and Reports, 1952-1957 (Box 60, Folder 6)
          - Family Schedules and Notes (Box 60, Folder 7)
          - Family Schedules and Notes (Box 60, Folder 8)
          - Revised Draft of Field Research Report (Box 61, Folder 1)
        - President's Commission on Migratory Labor. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1950.and Report,1951 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - American Country Life Association, Incorporated, 1948-1949 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - United States Children's Bureau, 1945-1951 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1950-1951 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Federal Aid to Education, 1947-1948 (Box 61, Folder 6, Box 80)
        - National Conference of State Counseling Supervisors,1958 (Box 63, Folder 6)
          - Printed Material Received by AGRY
            The Alliance for Guidance of Rural Youth received a great deal of miscellaneous printed material. This printed material has been arranged by agency (e.g. Department of State) and subject (e.g. Health). The categories are arbitrary and consequently there is considerable overlapping.
            - Department of State (Box 73, Folder 10)
            - Department of State (Box 81, Box 74, Folder 1)
            - Education (Box 74, Folder 2, Box 80)
            - Education (Box 74, Folder 3, Box 80)
            - Education (Box 74, Folder 4)
            - Education (Box 80, Box 81, Box 74, Folder 5)
            - Education (Box 74, Folder 6)
            - Education (Box 80, Box 75, Folder 1)
            - Education (Box 80, Box 75, Folder 2)
            - Employment Opportunities (Box 75, Folder 3)
            - Employment Opportunities (Box 80, Box 75, Folder 4)
            - Employment Opportunities (Box 80, Box 75, Folder 5)
            - Farmers and Farming (Box 75, Folder 6)
            - Federal (Box 75, Folder 7)
            - Federal. Fair Labor Standards Act, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 1)
            - Federal. Area Redevelopment Act, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 2, Box 80)
            - Federal (Box 76, Folder 3)
            - Federal (Box 76, Folder 4)
            - Guidance and Counseling (Box 76, Folder 5)
            - Guidance and Counseling (Box 76, Folder 6, Box 80)
            - Guidance and Counseling (Box 77, Folder 1, Box 80)
            - Guidance and Counseling (Box 77, Folder 2)
            - Guidance and Counseling (Box 80, Box 77, Folder 3)
            - Health (Box 77, Folder 4)
            - Health (Box 77, Folder 5, Box 80)
            - Health (Box 77, Folder 6, Box 80)
            - Migrant Workers (Box 80, Box 78, Folder 1)
            - Migrant Workers (Box 80, Box 78, Folder 2)
            - National Conference on the Community, 1947 (Box 78, Folder 3)
            - Psychology (Box 80, Box 78, Folder 4)
            - Religion (Box 78, Folder 5)
            - Rural Issues (Box 80, Box 78, Folder 6)
            - Youth and Child Labor (Box 78, Folder 7, Box 80)
            - Miscellany (Box 78, Folder 8)
            - Miscellany (Box 80, Box 79, Folder 1)
            - Miscellany (Box 79, Folder 2)
            - Miscellany (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Work Camps, 1947-1951 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - International Children's Emergency Fund, 1946-1947 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Kiplinger Service, 1948 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - National Defense Education Act Study
        Between 1960-1963 Warburton conducted a study of the effects of the National Defense Education Act Title V-A on guidance programs in rural secondary Schools. Title V-A allocated 15 million dollars a year (from 1958 to 1961) to stimulate guidance programs in secondary schools. This study was the last major project sponsored by the Alliance for Guidance of Rural Youth.
        Material from the study is divided into four groups: general, state, local, and material related to the book written about the study, Stimulating Guidance in Rural Schools (1964). A copy of the book is in Box 27.
        - Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 63, Folder 7)
        - Warburton's Personal Correspondence, 1961, March-April (Box 63, Folder 8)
        - Warburton's Trip Itinerary and Notes,1961 (Box 63, Folder 9)
        - Study Expense Statements, 1960-1964 (Box 64, Folder 1)
        - Drafts of Description of the Study Cover Letter (Box 64, Folder 2)
        - Drafts of Questionnaires for State Programs (Box 64, Folder 3)
        - Drafts of Questionnaires for Local Schools and Notes (Box 64, Folder 4)
        - Statements and Drafts of Statements Given Before Congress on NDEA, 1961-1963 (Box 64, Folder 5)
        - Bibliographies and Clippings, 1960-1962 (Box 64, Folder 6)
        - Printed Reference Material (Box 64, Folder 7)
        - Printed Reference Material (Box 64, Folder 8)
        - Printed Reference Material (Box 80, Box 65, Folder 1)
        - State Correspondence and Accompanying Material
          - Alabama, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 2)
          - Alaska, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 3)
          - Arizona, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 4)
          - Arkansas, 1960-1961 (Box 81, Box 65, Folder 5)
          - California, 1960-1961 (Box 81, Box 65, Folder 6)
          - Colorado, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 7)
          - Connecticut, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 8)
          - Delaware, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 9)
          - Florida, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 10)
          - Georgia, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 11)
          - Hawaii, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 12)
          - Idaho, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 13)
          - Illinois, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 1)
          - Indiana, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 2)
          - Iowa, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 3)
          - Kansas, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 4)
          - Kentucky, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 5)
          - Louisiana, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 6)
          - Maine, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 7)
          - Maryland, 1960-1961 (Box 81, Box 66, Folder 8)
          - Massachusetts, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 9)
          - Michigan, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 10)
          - Minnesota, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 11)
          - Mississippi, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 12)
          - Missouri, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 13)
          - Montana, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 1)
          - Nebraska, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 2)
          - Nevada, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 3)
          - New Hampshire, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 4)
          - New Jersey, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 5)
          - New Mexico, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 6)
          - New York, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 7)
          - New York, 1960 (Box 80, Box 67, Folder 8)
          - North Carolina, 1960-1962 (Box 67, Folder 9)
          - North Dakota, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 10)
          - Ohio, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 1)
          - Ohio, 1960 (Box 80, Box 68, Folder 2)
          - Ohio, 1960 (Box 80, Box 68, Folder 3)
          - Oklahoma, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 4)
          - Oregon, 1960-1961 (Box 68, Folder 5)
          - Pennsylvania, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 6)
          - Rhode Island, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 7)
          - South Carolina, 1960-1963 (Box 80, Box 68, Folder 8)
          - South Dakota, 1960-1963 (Box 68, Folder 9)
          - Tennessee, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 10)
          - Texas, 1960-1961 (Box 68, Folder 11)
          - Utah, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 12)
          - Vermont, 1960-1961 (Box 69, Folder 1)
          - Virginia, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 2)
          - Washington, 1960-1961 (Box 69, Folder 3)
          - West Virginia, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 4)
          - Wisconsin, 1960-1961 (Box 69, Folder 5)
          - Wyoming, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 6)
          - Puerto Rico, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 7)
        - Specific Rural High School Guidance Programs
          - Marana, Arizona. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1961 (Box 69, Folder 8)
          - Marana, Arizona. Student Essays (Box 69, Folder 9)
          - Fordyce, Arkansas. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1961 (Box 69, Folder 10)
          - Fordyce, Arkansas. Student Essays (Box 69, Folder 11)
          - Plumas County, California, Portola Junior-Senior High School. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1961 (Box 69, Folder 12)
          - Plumas County, California, Portola Junior-Senior High School. Student Essays (Box 69, Folder 13)
          - Leadville, Colorado. Student Essays (Box 69, Folder 14)
          - Leadville, Colorado. Assorted Material (Box 69, Folder 15)
          - Monte Vista, Colorado. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1961 (Box 69, Folder 16)
          - Monte Vista, Colorado. Student Essays (Box 69, Folder 17)
          - Alta, Iowa. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1961 (Box 70, Folder 1)
          - Alta, Iowa. Student Essays (Box 70, Folder 2)
          - Carlton, Minnesota. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1961 (Box 70, Folder 3)
          - Carlton, Minnesota. Student Essays (Box 70, Folder 4)
          - Stewartville, Minnesota. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1961 (Box 70, Folder 5)
          - Stewartville, Minnesota. Student Essays (Box 70, Folder 6)
          - Oakland, Mississippi. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1961 (Box 70, Folder 7)
          - Oakland, Mississippi. Student Essays from Oakland High School (for white students) (Box 70, Folder 8)
          - Oakland, Mississippi. Student Essays from Walker High School (for black students) (Box 70, Folder 9)
          - Franklin, New York. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1961 (Box 70, Folder 10)
          - Franklin, New York. Student Essays (Box 70, Folder 11)
          - Marion, New York. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1961 (Box 70, Folder 12)
          - Marion, New York. Student Essays (Box 71, Folder 1)
          - Marion, New York. Assorted Material (Box 71, Folder 2)
          - Mooers, New York. Student Essays (Box 71, Folder 3)
          - Jackson, North Carolina. Correspondence and accompanying Material, 1960-1961 (Box 71, Folder 4)
          - Jackson, North Carolina. Student Essays (Box 71, Folder 5)
          - Bloomdale, Ohio, Elmwood High School. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1961 (Box 71, Folder 6)
          - Bloomdale, Ohio, Elmwood High School. Student Essays (Box 71, Folder 7)
          - Coburg, Oregon. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1961 (Box 71, Folder 8)
          - Coburg, Oregon. Student Essays (Box 71, Folder 9)
          - Finn Rock, Oregon, McKenzie High School. Correspondence and Accompanying Material, 1961-1963 (Box 72, Folder 1)
          - Finn Rock, Oregon, McKenzie High School. Student Essays (Box 72, Folder 2)
          - Georgetown, South Carolina, Choppee High School. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1961 (Box 72, Folder 3)
          - Georgetown, South Carolina, Choppee High School. Student Essays (Box 72, Folder 4)
          - Green Sea, South Carolina. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1961 (Box 72, Folder 5)
          - Green Sea, South Carolina. Student Essays (Box 72, Folder 6)
          - Madison, South Dakota, General Beadle High School. Student Essays (Box 72, Folder 7)
          - Madison, South Dakota, General Beadle High School. Assorted Material (Box 72, Folder 8)
          - Mission, South Dakota, Todd County High School. Correspondence and Accompanying Material, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 9)
          - Mission, South Dakota, Todd County High School. Student Essays (Box 72, Folder 10)
          - Bristol, Vermont. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1961 (Box 72, Folder 11)
          - Bristol, Vermont. Student Essays (Box 72, Folder 12)
        - Material Related to Stimulating Guidance in Rural Schools
          - Publicity,1964 (Box 73, Folder 1)
          - Typed Answers to Questionnaires (Box 73, Folder 2)
          - Charts (Box 73, Folder 3)
          - Charts (Box 73, Folder 4)
          - Rough Draft of Manuscript (Box 73, Folder 5)
          - Draft of Manuscript (Box 73, Folder 6)
          - Draft of Chapters 1-4 (Box 73, Folder 7)
          - Draft of Chapters 5-7 (Box 73, Folder 8)
          - Clippings,1940's - 1950's (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - League of Women Voters. Action, 1947-1948 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - National Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1947 (Box 80, Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Parents' Magazine. Correspondence and Accompanying Material,1948 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Radio and Education, 1947-1949 (Box 80, Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Rural Youth of the U.S.A., 1948-1951and undated (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - Save the Children Foundation, 1947-1948 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - National School Health Services Act, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - School Lunch Program, 1947-1948 (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - U.N.E.S.C.O., 1947 (Box 61, Folder 18, Box 80)
      - Women's Bureau Conference, 1948 (Box 61, Folder 19)
      - National Citizens Commission on Public Schools. Correspondence and Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - National Citizens Commission on Public Schools. Printed Material and Clippings,1950 (Box 62, Folder 2, Box 81)
      - Hotels, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Warburton's Do Something About File, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Warburton's Paper Presentation in Maine. Correspondence and Accompanying Material, 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Warburton's Article for Education Magazine, Building Guidance for Rural Young People. Correspondence and Accompanying Material, 1953-1954 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Warburton's Things to Write About File, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Mid-Century White House Conference on Children and Youth
        - Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 62, Folder 8)
        - Correspondence and Notes, 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 9)
        - Programs, Meeting Minutes, and Reports, 1948-1950, Feb. (Box 62, Folder 10)
        - Programs, Meeting Minutes, and Reports, 1950, April-October (Box 62, Folder 11)
        - Programs, Meeting Minutes, and Reports, 1950, Nov.-Dec. (Box 63, Folder 1)
        - Programs, Meeting Minutes, and Reports, 1951-1952and undated (Box 63, Folder 2)
        - Ruth Strang's Article on the Conference, Concerted Action For and With Rural Youth, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 3)
        - Printed Material, 1949-1952 (Box 81, Box 63, Folder 4)
        - Printed Material and Clippings, 1950-1951 (Box 81, Box 63, Folder 5)
- Spellman College and Atlanta University Series, 1928-1932
  Warburton taught labor and economics at Spelman College and Atlanta University from 1929 to 1932. Material from this period includes speeches, course materials such as outlines, bibliographies, and student essays, printed material, ten issues of Crisis magazine, and clippings. The series also has correspondence, minutes, reports, printed material, and clippings from the Atlanta Forum Association, an organization devoted to bringing liberal speakers to Atlanta.
  Researchers would probably find the student autobiographies and a survey of standards of living in black districts in Atlanta the most fascinating primary material in the series. There is also a good group photograph of some students and faculty of Atlanta University (undated, but taken sometime during Warburton's tenure). The photograph is not in the series, but rather in an oversize folder.
  - Speeches, 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Contains drafts of speeches given by Warburton to local groups in 1929-1930.
  - Miscellany, 1929-1932 and undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Course Materials
    - Student Essays
      - Autobiographies (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Economics (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Economics (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Economics (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Economic History (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Industries of the United States (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Industries of the United States (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Student Projects
      - Survey of Standards of Living in Black Districts in Atlanta (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Teaching Material
      - Economics 21 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Economics 22 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Economics 33 and Economics 41 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Economic Theories (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Industries of the United States (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - American History 21 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Bibliographies and Book notices (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Miscellany (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Printed Material. Afro-Americans (Box 9, Folder 11, Box 80, Box 81)
  - Printed Material. Atlanta University, Morehouse College, and Spelman College (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Printed Material. Atlanta University and Spelman College (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Printed Material. Spelman College (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Printed Material. Miscellany (Box 10, Folder 4, Box 81)
  - Periodicals. Crisis Magazine, 1932, Feb.-Dec. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers. American Guardian, 1932, Feb.-May (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers. Labor Unity, April, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Clippings. Afro-Americans (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Clippings. Afro-Americans (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Clippings. Spain, 1929-1931 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Clippings. Miscellany (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Photograph of Some Students and Faculty of Atlanta University, undated (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Atlanta Forum Association
    - Correspondence, 1930, Sept.-Oct. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Nov. 1930 - Sept. 1931 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Minutes and Reports, 1930-1931 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Printed Material and Clippings, 1930-1931 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Federal Emergency Relief Administration Series, 1934-1935
  This series has correspondence, reports, printed material, and clippings from Warburton's work with the Federal Emergency Relief Administration. In 1934 Warburton directed training centers for teachers in Atlanta, Georgia, and Gulfport, Mississippi. In 1935 she directed a similar center in Logan, Utah. Interesting material includes letters and reports that highlight the difficulties of running programs designed to train unemployed teachers how to teach worker's education, as well as autobiographies of unemployed teachers.
  - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Reports, 1934-1935 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Printed Material and Clippings, 1934-1935 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Atlanta Training Center
    - Reports and Accompanying Material, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Printed Material. Worker's Journal, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Gulfport Training Center
    - Reports and Accompanying Material, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Student Papers, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Logan Training Center
    - Reports and Accompanying Material, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Student Papers, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Printed Material. The Worker's Kit, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Affiliated Schools for Workers Series, 1932-1935
  In 1935 Warburton studied an Affiliated Schools for Workers program in Detroit, Michigan. This series has material from her study, as well as a great deal of material concerned with other programs sponsored by the New Deal. There are reports, pamphlets, clippings, and printed material in the series. The bulk of the series is printed material, the most interesting of which is probably the reports of the Federal Emergency Relief Administration. Researchers should use this series in conjunction with the Federal Emergency Relief Administration Series.
  - Reports and Accompanying Material from Detroit, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Reports and Accompanying Material from Detroit, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Miscellany, 1933-1935 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Clippings. Academic Freedom - Child Labor (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Clippings. Coal Industry - Income (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Clippings. New Deal - Women (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Clippings and Reprints, 1932-1935 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Clippings and Reprints, 1934-1935 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Clippings and Reprints, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Printed Material
    - Congressional Bills, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Reports of the Committee on Economic Security, 1933-1935 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Reports of the Federal Emergency Relief Administration, 1934-1935 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Reports of the Federal Emergency Relief Administration, 1934-1935 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Reports of the Federal Emergency Relief Administration, 1934-1935 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Reports and Bibliographies (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Reports and Bibliographies (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Reports and Bibliographies (Box 15, Folder 2, Box 81)
    - Miscellany, 1933-1935 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Miscellany, 1933-1935 (Box 15, Folder 4, Box 81)
    - Miscellany, 1933-1935 (Box 15, Folder 5, Box 81)
    - Periodicals and Newsletters, 1932-1935 (Box 15, Folder 6)